Thank you for watching!
Kettle and Idol
And now the third one.
Yes, sir.
I love you too, Rainbow.
It's 8 o'clock, right?
Yes, I really love it.
There's probably no episode I haven't seen.
I've seen it three times.
Do you have any recommendations?
There are many.
First of all, the set of the house is really amazing.
You should buy one.
I really like comedy.
In one of them, Moshimura Ken-san plays a detective.
We went to a house that was rumored to be haunted.
In front of Shimuraken-san, ghosts appeared all the time, but when other people came
But when other people come, they don't show up.
But when other people come, they don't appear.
I really love that one.
I can talk about it.
This is it.
It's the end.
Yes, sir.
Ger answer.
I see.
I've been doing this for a long time, but...
Ms. Chousuke Ikaria will play the role of the mother.
Yes, sir.
And the other four play the children.
Yes...
The first one is "Ikaria Kyousuke"...
No, no, no, he's an Icaria Kyoshu. He was already a male in front of my TV.
I'd like to go talk to him.
I'd like to see him do a comedy show with a big set at his house.
With the members of Ibichi.
I know it's a lot of work, but would you be interested in doing it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You want to make Ebichu a comedy group?
Yes, I would like to do it.
But then...
It would be nice to do it live.
I think it would be interesting to have a live performance of just comedy.
This is just something I want to do.
The two times I felt the most empathy this year
That's great.
By the way, who will play the role of Ms. Ikaria?
Mayama or Rika-chan?
Mayama.
She's always the youngest and the most important person in the group.
So it's a role that other people don't like.
That's just for Ikaria.
She made a face that was hard to say.
Like, "What are you talking about?
Mayama, Ikaria, and Ikaria's theory
Yes, sir.
So, what about you, Kazomi?
What do you want to do?
Uh, me? I'm, uh, I don't know who I am.
I think I'm supposed to play the role of Shimura Ken-san, who is really the best actor in the role.
There are so many people. But that's all right.
By the way, Takagi-boo's role is
I don't mean that he takes the initiative in making fun of things, but he is a bit funny.
But I think it's a role where you can say something funny and sometimes funny.
Like Sakayagi Cocona.
I see.
She sometimes says really weird things.
She's also a little bit funny. That's how weird she is.
She says the strangest things.
I'd like you to do it.
Well, I'd love to see that.
I'd like to see that.
It would be nice.
I'd like to see a set like that.
I'd love to see you do a contrivance.
Please let us do a contrivance like "All Together at 8:00" this time.
This show is for you, Tomoki.
Mr. Montach
No Nickname
Chiaaki-san
This program was provided by Jai.
Thank you very much.